Guide to the Henry W. Jones Papers, circa 1906-1948 and undated RL.11148
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Henry W. Jones papers
circa 1906-1948 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jones, Henry W.
RL.11148
0.2 Linear Feet
Advertising executive in Ohio and Pennsylvania, Manager for the United Manufacturing Company and other mail order and direct sales companies.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Henry W. Jones Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2015.
Collection Overview
Correspondence, brochures and mail order sales training manuals and other printed materials pertaining to Jones career in direct marketing and mail order. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising -- United States; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising, Direct marketing -- History; Advertising, Direct-mail -- United States; Direct marketing -- United States; Jones, Henry W.
- Bookseller description card, undated (Box 1)
- Breuer & Son, New York, N.Y., 1912 (Box 1)
- Chicago (includes Trade Circular Addressing Company), 1912 (Box 1)
- Cincinnati, 1912 (Box 1)
- Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1906-1912 and undated (Box 1)
- East Libery Presbyterian Church, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1948 (Box 1)
- James Brown Company, Jonesville, Miss. (includes brochure Cinch Tire Repair Kit), undated (Box 1)
- Mail Order World, 1912 (Box 1)
- Miller & Co., Muskegon, Mich., undated (Box 1)
- New York American, 1912 (Box 1)
- Niagara Merchandising Co., Lockport, N.Y. (includes mail order training brochure), 1910-1912 (Box 1)
- Niagara Merchandising Co., Lockport, N.Y. (includes mail order training brochure) (Box 1)
- William A. Heacock, mail order training publications, undated (Box 1)